Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
- Interns & Residents Bulletin, Publication (Box 222, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: An open letter to the Lincoln Community, 1977; Publication (Box 222, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Interns & Residents Bulletin, 1974; Publication (Box 222, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol.3:no.5 (1974:Sept.)
- Iron and Bronze Workers, Publication (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: To all Iron and Bronze Workers, 1927; Publication (Box 223, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Association of Iron, Steel & Tin Workers, Publication (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Official program & souvenir, thirty first Annual convention of the Amalgamated Association of Iron, Steel & Tin Workers, 1906; Publication (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Western scales of prices governing wages in Rollin Mills for the year ending June 30, 1907., Publication (Box 223, Folder 2)
- Iron Workers, Publication (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Address delivered by George Meanyat the 30th Convention, 1956; Publication (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: California Ironworkers field welfare plan, 1959; Publication (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Health & Welfare Plan, Northwest Iron Workers, 1955; Publication (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Iron Workers, District Council, Western, New York and Vicinity, Welfare Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Iron Workers, Local 455, Pension fund, 1959; Publication (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Iron Workers, Locals 40 and 361, Welfare fund, 1949; Publication (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Ironclad safety code, Publication (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Ironworker Apprentice, record book, 1958; Publication (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Ironworkers' Intermountain Health and Welfare Fund, 1955; Publication (Box 223, Folder 3)
    Author: Ironworkers' Intermountain Health and Welfare Fund
  - Item 10: The Blueprint, what it is and how to read it, 1950; Publication (Box 223, Folder 3)
- Iron Workers, Publication (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Iron Workers Local 455, Pension Fund, 1962; Publication (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Iron Workers Local 455, Welfare fund, 1963; Publication (Box 223, Folder 4)
- Iron Workers, Publication (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: 16 steel workers remain on strike at Memorial after 'short hour' week brings protest walkout, 1949-1963 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: 2,500 to benefit in welfare plan, 1949-1963 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: 8 workers to be polled on union affiliation, 1949-1963 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Atomic picketing ban extended, 1949-1963 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Bridge men get contract, 1949-1963 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Cardinal gets union card, 1949-1963 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Ironworkers are still off jobs, 1949-1963 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Memorial workers seek six-day week, 1949-1963 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Picket pulled, but job at church still halted, 1949-1963 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Short strike halts work at church, 1949-1963 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Thruway iron workers returned to work, 1949-1963 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Thruway iron workers walk off job, 1949-1963 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Union found guilty of costing man's job, 1949-1963 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: 2,500 defy unions on atomic halt, 1949-1963 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Northwest adds cost of strikes, 1949-1963 (Box 223, Folder 5)
- Iron Workers, Publication (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Reports of General Pres., General Sec., General Treasurer, General Exec. Bd. And General Exec. Council to the 33rd Convention, 1968; Publication (Box 223, Folder 6)
- International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Ironworkers, Publication (Box 223, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Official directory, 1971; Publication (Box 223, Folder 7)
    Author: International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Ironworkers
    Notes: 1971 (Aug, Nov., May, Feb.)
- International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Ironworkers, Publication (Box 223, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: A new concept in training for the construction industry, 1973; Publication (Box 223, Folder 8)
    Author: National Ironworkers and Employers Training Program
  - Item 2: Official Directory, 1972; Publication (Box 223, Folder 8)
    Notes: 1972 (Feb.)
  - Item 3: Reports of General Pres., General Sec., General Treasurer, General Exec. Bd. And General Exec. Council to the 34th Convention, 1972; Publication (Box 223, Folder 8)
- International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Ironworkers, Publication (Box 223, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: quarterly audit report, 1947; Publication (Box 223, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Report on examination of recorded cash receipts and disbursements of the various funds for the three months ended (Dec. 31, 1946 & June 30, 1946), Publication (Box 223, Folder 9)
- International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Ironworkers, Publication (Box 223, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Resolution.the following resolution endorsing the candidacy of Pres. Lyndon B. Johnson.32nd Convention of the International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Ironworkers, 1964; Publication (Box 223, Folder 10)
- International Jewelry Workers' Union, Publication (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Pension fund, 1969; Publication (Box 224, Folder 1)
    Author: International Jewelry Workers' Union
- Industrial Bulletin, Publication (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Barriers coming down, 1965; Publication (Box 224, Folder 2)
    Notes: article from the Industrial Bulletin
  - Item 2: He scores a strike!, 1965; Publication (Box 224, Folder 2)
- International Jewelry Workers' Union, Publication (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: correspondence, 1948; Publication (Box 224, Folder 3)
    Author: International Jewelry Workers' Union. Local 1
  - Item 2: Insurance plan, benefits report, 1949; Publication (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Meet your union, a booklet for members, 1949; Publication (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Minutes of General Executive Board, 1948; Publication (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Why you should join, 1949; Publication (Box 224, Folder 3)
- International Jewelry Workers' Union, Publication (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Jewelers, though we want peace it may be war!, Publication (Box 224, Folder 4)
- International Jewelry Workers' Union, Publication (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Jewelry Workers' Annual - 1902, Publication (Box 224, Folder 5)
    Notes: Photocopy
- International Jewelry Workers' Union, Publication (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Jewelry Workers' Annual - 1902, Publication (Box 224, Folder 6)
    Notes: Original copy
- International Jewelry Workers' Union, Publication (Box 224, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Jewelry Worker's bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 224, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.11:no.1-4, 6- 9
- JLC (Jewish Labor Committee), Publication (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Let's be human, 1969-1971 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    Author: Harry Fleischman
    Notes: Issues from 1969- 1971
  - Item 2: The Jewish labor movement: a living legacy, Publication (Box 225, Folder 1)
    Author: Gus Tyler
  - Item 3: The A.F. of L. fights bigotry!, 1940; Publication (Box 225, Folder 1)
    Author: Jewish Labor Committee (U.S.)
  - Item 4: The Jewish Labor Movement in America: two views, 1957; Publication (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Fear, frustration, backlash: the new crisis in civil rights, 1966; Publication (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The common enemy of mankind, 1942; Publication (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: In freedom's cause: report, 1957; Publication (Box 225, Folder 1)
    Author: Jewish Labor Committee (U.S.).
    Notes: Anti-Discrimination Dept. Biennial Convention (Atlantic, N.J. 1957)
  - Item 8: To build a new world., 1965; Publication (Box 225, Folder 1)
    Author: Thomas R. Brooks
  - Item 9: Jewish labor hits Soviet anti-Semitism, 1953; Publication (Box 225, Folder 1)
- JLC (Jewish Labor Committee), Publication (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Pioneers of American Unionism, 1943; Publication (Box 225, Folder 2)
    Author: Samuel Colton
  - Item 2: Memorandums, 1960-1967 (Box 225, Folder 2)
    Author: Jewish Labor Committee
  - Item 3: JLC National Trade Union Council for Human Rights, Publication (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: What is Brotherhood?, Publication (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: The Challenge we face, Publication (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Fighter for human rights, Publication (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: JLC Labor Civil Rights Conference, Publication (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: NY JLC Report, 1968; Publication (Box 225, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1 (1968)
- JLC (Jewish Labor Committee), Publication (Box 225, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labor reports, 1960; Publication (Box 225, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.18:no.149-151 (1960)
  - Item 2: Labor reports, 1962; Publication (Box 225, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.20:no.163-167, 169-172 (1962)
  - Item 3: Labor reports, 1963; Publication (Box 225, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.21:no.173-178 (1963)
- JLC (Jewish Labor Committee), Publication (Box 225, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor reports, 1960; Publication (Box 225, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.18:no.141-147 (1960)
  - Item 2: Labor reports, 1961; Publication (Box 225, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.19:no.148, 152 -162 (1961)
  - Item 3: Labor reports, 1963; Publication (Box 225, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.21:no.179 (1963)
- JLC (Jewish Labor Committee), Publication (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor reports, 1958; Publication (Box 225, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.16:no.119-129 (1958)
  - Item 2: Labor reports, 1959; Publication (Box 225, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.17:no.130-136, 138-140 (1959)
- JLC (Jewish Labor Committee), Publication (Box 225, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Labor reports, 1956; Publication (Box 225, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.14:no.101-110 (1956)
  - Item 2: Labor reports, 1957; Publication (Box 225, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.15:no.111-121 (1957)
- JLC (Jewish Labor Committee), Publication (Box 225, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Labor reports, 1955; Publication (Box 225, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.13:no.91-100 (1955)
  - Item 2: Labor reports, 1953; Publication (Box 225, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.11:no.69-70, 72,76-79, 81-88 (1953-1954)
  - Item 3: Labor reports, 1954; Publication (Box 225, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.12:no.89-90 (1954)
- JLC (Jewish Labor Committee), Publication (Box 226, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: American labor to the rescue: addresses delivered by prominent American and European leaders of labor at the opening session of the National Conference of the Jewish Labor Committee held at Carnegie Hall, New York City on January 17th, 1941, Publication (Box 226, Folder 1)
    Author: National Conference of the Jewish Labor Committee
- JLC (Jewish Labor Committee), Publication (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Labor looks at the crisis in civil rights, 1959; Publication (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Communist anti-Semitism: a factual up-to-date report made to the Jewish Labor Committee annual conference, Atlantic City, April 17-18th, 1953., Publication (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Jewish labor fights Communism, Publication (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Intolerance your greatest enemy, Publication (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: if it means death itself, I will pay it, Publication (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: It's your law, too!, Publication (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The McCarran-Walter Law?, Publication (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Rumor clinic, Publication (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: In convention assembled, welfare, economy, education, Civil rights, Publication (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Blessings of Freedom, Publication (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: The new line of the Communist Party, Publication (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: The CIO News..., Publication (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: What is brotherhood?, Publication (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: The new line of the Communist Party, Publication (Box 226, Folder 2)
- JLC (Jewish Labor Committee), Publication (Box 226, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labor and civil rights, 1959; Publication (Box 226, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The fate of Soviet Jewry: the Jews in the Soviet Union.: Soviet-Yiddish literature, 1918-1948, 1957; Publication (Box 226, Folder 3)
    Author: Elias Schulman
  - Item 3: We call all men brothers, 1957; Publication (Box 226, Folder 3)
    Author: George Meany
  - Item 4: Human rights: cornerstone of freedom - an address by Arthur J. Goldberg, 1955; Publication (Box 226, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: A program for freedom, 1955; Publication (Box 226, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Israel strikes at bases of Egyptian aggression: acts in self-defense, 1956; Publication (Box 226, Folder 3)
    Author: Abba Solomon Eban
- JLC (Jewish Labor Committee), Publication (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Matter of fact, by Joseph and Stewart Alsop, 1956; Publication (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: background and fact sheet - Arab assault on civil rights within the US; American labor on the Middle East crisis; The Middle East conflict, 1956-1957 (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: memorandums -, 1956-1959 (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: It's your law, too!, 1955; Publication (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Jewish labor unit fights for civil rights, liberties, 1955; Publication (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: AFL-CIO Merger Convention, NYC, 1955; Publication (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Human rights: suggested readings for Union and Librarians, 1956; Publication (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: educational mat'l. - 6 outlines for group discussion, 1958; Publication (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: The responsibility of the North in the desegregation crisis in the south, 1957; Publication (Box 226, Folder 4)
    Author: Emanuel Muravchik
- JLC (Jewish Labor Committee), Publication (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Reports, materials, resolutions (Biennial Convention, May, 1957), Publication (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Civil rights platform plank, Publication (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: American labor and racial equality, 1952; Publication (Box 226, Folder 5)
    Notes: Reprinted from Labor Reports. 2 copies
  - Item 4: Organized labor knows the score; Remove the barriers!, Publication (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Prejudice is expensive, Publication (Box 226, Folder 5)
    Author: Leo Cherne
    Notes: Reprinted from Labor Reports.
  - Item 6: Labor's role in race relations, Publication (Box 226, Folder 5)
    Author: Emil Rieve
  - Item 7: Toward a better, stronger America, Publication (Box 226, Folder 5)
    Author: A. J. Hayes
  - Item 8: You can't buy brotherhood, Publication (Box 226, Folder 5)
    Author: Walter P. Reuther
  - Item 9: Hatred breeds oppression, Publication (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: We can run but we can't hide, 1952; Publication (Box 226, Folder 5)
    Author: Victor G. Reuther
  - Item 11: AFL-CIO calls for just peace in the Middle East, 1960; Publication (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: What are we waiting for?, 1952; Publication (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: There are no inferior races!, 1952; Publication (Box 226, Folder 5)
    Author: John Haynes Holmes
  - Item 14: Prejudice must be fought, 1952; Publication (Box 226, Folder 5)
    Author: Philip Murray
- JLC (Jewish Labor Committee), Publication (Box 226, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: What is the Jewish Labor Committee, Publication (Box 226, Folder 6)
- Ernesto Galarza, Publication (Box 226, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Strangers in our fields, 1957; Publication (Box 226, Folder 7)
    Author: Ernesto Galarza
- State Society of Labor and Industry, Publication (Box 226, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Proceedings Sixth annual convention, 1904; Publication (Box 226, Folder 8)
    Author: State Society of Labor and Industry
- Allied Kingsport Press Unions, Publication (Box 226, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: correspondence, 1964; Publication (Box 226, Folder 9)
    Author: Allied Kingsport Press Unions
  - Item 2: March 11, 1963 to.?? WHY, Publication (Box 226, Folder 9)
- New York Protective Associations, Publication (Box 226, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Official journal, 1899-1900 (Box 226, Folder 10)
    Author: New York Protective Associations
  - Item 2: Sanctuary of District Assembly 126, Why general officers should be deposed, Publication (Box 226, Folder 10)
    Author: Knights of Labor
    Notes: Transcript of speech
  - Item 3: District Assembly - Forty-Nine - journal, 1949; Publication (Box 226, Folder 10)
    Notes: Very brittle
- Knights of Labor, Publication (Box 226, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Dues card, Publication (Box 226, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Reasons for the growth of the Knights of Labor in 1885-1886, 1950; Publication (Box 226, Folder 11)
    Author: Donald L. Kemmerer
    Notes: Reprinted from the Industrial and Labor Relations Review, vol.3:no.2. 2 copies
- Knights of Labor, Publication (Box 226, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: David B. Hill - Knights of Labor repudiate and denounce him, 1888; Publication (Box 226, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Address of The Congress of the Knights of Labor of the State of New York to the Sovereign electors, 1896; Publication (Box 226, Folder 12)
    Notes: An official expose of railroad mismanagment in New York State
  - Item 3: Letter from J.N. Corbin to Arthur Holder, 1887; Publication (Box 226, Folder 12)
    Author: J. N. Corbin
    Notes: re: Organization of railroad employees and the problems of the Union Pacific Organization
  - Item 4: Union Pacific Employees Magazine, Publication (Box 226, Folder 12)
    Notes: Monthly magazine devoted to the interests of employer and employee
  - Item 5: Noble and Holy Order petition, 1882; Publication (Box 226, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Ritual booklet, Publication (Box 226, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Adelphon kruptos; the Full, illustrated ritual; including the Unwritten Work and an Historical Sketch of the Order, 1886; Publication (Box 226, Folder 12)
    Notes: Bound in one book
- Coffeyville dynamite outrage, Publication (Box 226, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The plot unfolded! or, A history of the famous Coffeyville dynamite outrage, October 18, 1888, Publication (Box 226, Folder 13)
    Notes: One copy Very Brittle, and one conservation copy
- Labor Bureau, Inc., Publication (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Annual report, 1921; Publication (Box 227, Folder 1)
    Author: Labor Bureau, Inc.
  - Item 2: Annual report, 1927; Publication (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Facts win in labor disputes, 1943; Publication (Box 227, Folder 1)
- Labor Institute on Human Relations, Publication (Box 227, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Official call to the eighth annual.., 1953; Publication (Box 227, Folder 2)
    Author: Labor Institute on Human Relations
  - Item 2: Labor Committee to Combat Intolerance of Western New York, 1952; Publication (Box 227, Folder 2)
- LEA (Labor Education Association), Publication (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: memorandum, 1964; Publication (Box 227, Folder 3)
    Author: AID Labor Education Advisory Committee
  - Item 2: Report of Acting Director, Quarterly meeting, 1947; Publication (Box 227, Folder 3)
    Author: Labor Education Association (Philadelphia, Pa.)
  - Item 3: correspondence, 1947; Publication (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Forging ahead with LEA: masters of our fate, through unions of our choosing, Publication (Box 227, Folder 3)
- Labor Film Service, Publication (Box 227, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Presenting The Motion Picture, in its relations and possibilities for Labor and Human Betterment..., Publication (Box 227, Folder 4)
    Author: Labor Film Service
- Matthew Woll, Publication (Box 227, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor and intergroup harmony, 1952; Publication (Box 227, Folder 5)
    Author: Matthew Woll
- United Labor League of Ohio, Publication (Box 227, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Robert Alphonso Taft story, 1950; Publication (Box 227, Folder 6)
    Author: United Labor League of Ohio
- Labor Research Association, Publication (Box 227, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: How the crisis hit the auto workers, 1932; Publication (Box 227, Folder 7)
    Author: Labor Research Association (U.S.)
    Notes: Press Release
  - Item 2: How the NLRB can stop union violence, 1958; Publication (Box 227, Folder 7)
    Author: Sylvester Petro
- Labor Research Association, Publication (Box 227, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The history of the shorter workday, 1942; Publication (Box 227, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Railroads in crisis: a program for re-employment, rehabilitation and government ownership, 1939; Publication (Box 227, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: People's capitalism; stock ownership and production, 1958; Publication (Box 227, Folder 8)
    Author: J. M. Budish
  - Item 4: Billionaire corporations, their growth and power., 1954; Publication (Box 227, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: The bonus march, 1932; Publication (Box 227, Folder 8)
    Author: Felix Morrow
  - Item 6: Wages and profits in wartime, 1941; Publication (Box 227, Folder 8)
- Labor Research Association, Publication (Box 227, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Wages and profits in wartime, 1941; Publication (Box 227, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Monopoly in the United States, 1942; Publication (Box 227, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: The yellow dog contract, 1932; Publication (Box 227, Folder 9)
    Author: Elliot Ettelson Cohen
  - Item 4: U.S. and the Philippines, 1958; Publication (Box 227, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: The burden of taxes, 1956; Publication (Box 227, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Trade union facts, 1939; Publication (Box 227, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Poverty: its roots and its future, 1965; Publication (Box 227, Folder 9)
    Author: Hyman Lumer
  - Item 8: Disarmament and the American economy, 1960; Publication (Box 227, Folder 9)
    Author: Herbert Aptheker
- Blanche Bernstein, Publication (Box 227, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Roosevelt's relief record, 1936; Publication (Box 227, Folder 10)
    Author: Blanche Bernstein
- Institute of International Labor Research, Publication (Box 227, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Soviet colonialism, Publication (Box 227, Folder 11)
    Author: Institute of International Labor Research
- Newspaper clippings, Publication (Box 227, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: This union will befriend alien labor, Publication (Box 227, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: An die deutchen gewerkschaften New Yorks!, 1900-1902 (Box 227, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Report of Counsel for the period of three months, from August 1st to October 31st, 1902, Publication (Box 227, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Statuten des Arbeiter = Sekretariat's, 1900-1902 (Box 227, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Annual report of the Labor Secretariat, 1902; Publication (Box 227, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Arbeiter und Kameraden!, 1900; Publication (Box 227, Folder 12)
- Labor Zionist Organization of America-Poale Zion, Publication (Box 227, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: What Labor Zionism means to me, 1949; Publication (Box 227, Folder 13)
    Author: Max Lerner
  - Item 2: Labor Zionism and you, Publication (Box 227, Folder 13)
    Author: Labor Zionist Organization of America-Poale Zion
- Newspaper clippings, Publication (Box 227, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Labor 3D party urged, 1950; Publication (Box 227, Folder 14)
- Plasterers Helpers', Local No. 30, Publication (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labor through the years, 1950; Publication (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 228, Folder 1)
    Author: Plasterers Helpers', Local No. 30
- Laborers' International Union of North America, Publication (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: 15th Convention: Proposals of the General Executive Bd., 1966; Publication (Box 228, Folder 2)
    Author: Laborers' International Union of North America
  - Item 2: 15th Convention: Official list of Delegates, 1966; Publication (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: 15th Convention: Appeals, 1966; Publication (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: 15th Convention: Resolutions, 1966; Publication (Box 228, Folder 2)